

CONTACT

PHONE

+375 (29) 6670960

EMAIL

develop.evg@gmail.com

ADDRESS

BELARUS, MINSK











SKILLS

- REACT/REDUX/THUNK
- JAVASCRIPT/TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS/REST API
- ANT DESIGN/MATERIAL-UI
- HTML/CSS
- UNIT TESTS/STORYBOOK
- GIT
- FIGMA | POSTMAN
- WORDPRESS
- REACT-ROUTER-DOM, FORMIK & REDUX-

FORM

LANGUAGE

- English intermediate (B1)
- Russian native

EDUCATION

2021-2022 **IT-INCUBATOR** Frontend developer (React/Redux/TypeScript)

> 2010-2015 **Belarusian State University** THE FACULTY OF BIOLOGY (molecular biology)

YAUHENIYA KAZHAMIAKA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am a person who has a strong passion for programming that inspires me everyday. I have experience in creating SPA with React/Redux/TypeScript in team. Now I improve my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. I spend my leisure time on Codewars or by improving english skills. Open to your suggestions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER.

February 2023 - Present

ITPM Community (full-time) Achievements:

- Set up a working environment.
- Developed and maintained SPA on React from scratch.
- Successfully linked frontend and backend api.
- Designed and designed web pages, including complex forms
- · creating and editing a list of experts.
- Created a responsive design for several web pages.
- Translated the project from physical CSS properties to logical ones.
- Managed application performance.
- Brought the project to MVP 1.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

August 2021 - January 2023

- Took part in creating learning app, developed login page, modal windows, tests, menu and design.
- Use next technologies: React/Redux /ReduxThunk /RestApi / Axios /ReduxForm /Formik /MaterialUI /SCSS, etc.
- Check the correctness of the logic with unit tests and use Storybook for demonstration of individual modules of the application.
- Use TypeScript for better code control.

CHEMIST

July 2015 - June 2022

- Work on high-tech equipment.
- Development of methods for the determination of chemicals.
- Conducting audits, laboratory accreditation.

PROJECT WORK

Web admin panel for Chat Control

Telegram bot with a Web admin panel for ITPM Community Chat will help community members gain new knowledge, improve their skills, create new discussions between members, provide useful information and some entertaining material.

GitLab link

SOCIAL NETWORK

React/Redux-Toolkit/React-router-dom v6/Axios /Material UI/Formik/SCSS/Git, Github Creating learning app in team with using git, work with axios(CRUD) GitHub link

React-Pizza

React/Redux-Toolkit/React-router-dom v6/Axios /Material UI/Formik/SCSS/Git, Github Creating learning app in team with using git, work with axios(CRUD) GitHub link